

### ANTON CERNEAVSCHII

#### UNITY DEVELOPER

#### **PERSONAL DATA**

Good day, I am a Unity game developer with over a 3 years experience. I have experience in working with 3D development in a Unity, knowledge in C # and languages close to it. In addition, I have experience in Unity development, related to the customization of the input systems in Unity, with multiplayer based on Photon PUN, hyper casual games android/iOS development.

Also I have experience with procedural mesh generation, creating basic shaders, various plugins

for Unity, algorithms, many different assets Have experience in work with augmented reality: with markerless and marker-based projects.

Additionally worked with C, C++ programming and game development based on SFML graphics library and MFC.

### **SKILLS**

- -Unity 2D, 3D development
- -C# development
- -Git Version Contro
- -Zenject, ESC, Jobs
- -Game design
- -C/C++ development
- -HTML, CSS, JS knowledges

### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

email: cherneavschii.anton@gmail.com linkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anton-cernyavskiy-8a7995209/

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Unity Developer Blue Gravity Studios (2022 - 2023)

Working with midcore projects, with full development cycle.
Creating game architecture.
Working with ECS, DI (Zenject).
Development of "ultiplayer core (based on NetCode for GameObjects

## Unity Developer TryMyGames SRL (2021 - 2022)

2D, 3D Unity development.
Hyper casual games, casual games development.
Game Creating full cycle management.
Various plugins, assets for game development.
Working with procedural meshes, splines, Zenject, ECS.
Working with Shaders based on Shader Graph.

### **Unity Developer**

Midnight Works (2020-2021)

3D development in a Unity.

Multiplayer based on Photon PUN.

Hyper casual games android/iOS development.

Casual games development.

Procedural mesh generation, creating basic shaders, various. pluginsfor Unity, algorithms, many different assets.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Technical University of Moldova**Biomedical engineer

Licence - 2019 - 2023

### **INTERESTS AND HOBBIES**

I love coffee, music, mathematics, physics, programming.

### **WORK EXAMPLES**

Dive into projects created with my linkedIn profile:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anton-cernyavskiy-8a7995209/details/projects/